trysensa.com 2014-06-25

# Sensa Products, LLC Privacy Policy

**Effective January 01, 2011**  
If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order pages. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date) otherwise we cannot process your order. We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.  
  
We collect personal information not only to fulfill your order, but also to make our services more rewarding for you to use. We usually use this information for internal purposes, such as studying our customers' preferences and improving the customer experience. We may also use your information to contact you for account and promotional purposes, including trusted third party promotions.

We may share your personal information with companies that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, conducting surveys, providing customer service, and other similar functions. Such companies may have access to your personal information in order to perform their roles, but they may not disclose your information for other purposes.  
Personal information may be transferred in connection with the sale, merger, or acquisition of business assets of SENSA Products, LLC or its parent company. We may share aggregate web site usage information with marketing partners and affiliates, however, this information does not identify individual users. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us.  
We may also utilize information you have posted on community forums and message boards for use in marketing and promotions.   
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our site, please contact us as indicated below.  
  
We may occasionally send you information on special offers, promotions, or product updates, or you may be a subscriber to our newsletters or you may have opted in to receive newsletters or special promotions from one of our trusted third party providers. If you ever decide you no longer wish to receive these communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication, or by contacting the SENSA® Products Customer Service Team on our [contact page](http://www.sensa.com/contact-us.htm) or by writing to us at the address below.  
  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to collect anonymous information about how you use this site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave our site. The cookies are not connected to your personal information.  
  
"Web beacons" or clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We utilize web beacons that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. We do not tie the information gathered by web beacons to your personally identifiable information.  
  
This site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.  
  
Children under 13 may view our site, but they cannot make a purchase, nor provide any personal information. Our site is not designed for children and we do not wish to collect personal information from children under 13. If you register with us and we discover that you are under 13, we will delete your registration. We will send you a message if we do this.  
  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of the change. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  
  
If you have any questions regarding the use of our site or our privacy policy, or if you would like to request a copy of the National Advertising Division's Case Report on SENSA®'s marketing claims substantiation, please contact us at:

SENSA Products, LLC  
28516 Livingston Ave  
Valencia, CA 91355

Or call (866) 514-2554  
Mon-Fri 7:00am to 4:00pm PST
